<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Ronny A. Hernández Mora</title>
    <link>http://ronnyale.com/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Ronny A. Hernández Mora</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ronnyale.com/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>gitear</title>
      <link>http://ronnyale.com/project/gitear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ronnyale.com/project/gitear/</guid>
      <description>gitear is a package that can connect to the gitea API and take the data you need in a tidy format.      Overview     If you are using gitea as your self-hosting git service and also, you are an R user, gitear have functions build around the API to request your data and present it to you in a tidy format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ixplorer</title>
      <link>http://ronnyale.com/project/ixplorer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ronnyale.com/project/ixplorer/</guid>
      <description>ixplorer is a package that allows users to create, close or review issues without leaving their RStudio session.      What is ixplorer?     ixplorer is an R package built around gitea which is a self-hosting git service option. The ixplorer package allows the user to review, open, and close issues for specific repositories through an interface or through functions. This involves the use of an addin within RStudio that opens an interface created with shiny, shinyWidgets, and miniUI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lacrmr</title>
      <link>http://ronnyale.com/project/lacrmr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ronnyale.com/project/lacrmr/</guid>
      <description>lacrmr is a package that can connect to your CRM, obtain your customers data and, goals in a tidy way so you can craete and analyze your business metrics.      Overview     If you have a business or an organization that uses Less Annoying CRM to manage contacts but also you are an R user, probably you will want to get your customer relationship data into R and do your own analysis or even to automate your monthly reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rTLS</title>
      <link>http://ronnyale.com/project/rtls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ronnyale.com/project/rtls/</guid>
      <description>rTLS is an R package to that compiles a series of tools to process and calculate metrics on point clouds derived from Terrestrial Laser Scanners (TLS), also know as Terrestrial-Light Detection and Ranging (T-LiDAR).      Overview     rTLS goal is to provide a single environment to process point clouds as fast as it can be done. That it is why the rTLS coding has been evolving using different packages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
